Frustration with slow innovation in education.
AI offers the opportunity to disrupt the education system.
Rebuilding education from the ground up using AI.
One missing skill = overlooked candidate
Skills gap affects millions globally
Current training: expensive, generic, time-intensive
Expensive, generic courses requiring months of commitment.
The current education model is fundamentally broken.
PresGen Core: Generates tailored presentations.
PresGen Data: Analyzes data and inserts intelligent charts.
PresGen Video: Transforms content into engaging videos.
Presgen Training: Creates avatar-narrated courses.
Advanced models → better content generation
OpenAI mentorship → optimized education AI
Job seekers overlooked due to missing specific skills.
AI-powered education for everyone
Grove partnership = global impact
Ready to revolutionize learning