Identified workflow obstacles hindering sales team success at All Cloud.
Generated over $1 million in training revenue at AWS by focusing on behavioral change.
Built Presgen, a platform addressing real sales enablement challenges with AI-driven solutions.
Focus on identifying and eliminating real workflow obstacles.
Design systems that change behavior, not just transfer knowledge.
Measure results through tangible business outcomes, like reduced ramp times.
Presgen is an AI platform built to address real sales team challenges.
Features video editing and auto-presentation capabilities.
Demonstrates a commitment to innovation and practical problem-solving.
Proven ability to transform how teams work through innovative solutions.