Identified workflow obstacles hindering sales team effectiveness.
Designed systems to eliminate barriers and accelerate success.
Measured results through tangible business outcomes, like reduced ramp-up times.
Presgen was created to solve the workflow problems hindering sales teams.
The platform automates presentation creation and video editing.
It enables faster content creation and consistent messaging.
Reduced new hire ramp times from weeks to days.
Ensured consistent messaging across hundreds of countries.
Generated over $1 million in training revenue at AWS.
Bringing a proven track record of innovation and results.