27 years of technical instruction experience
Built Presgen, a platform to solve real sales enablement challenges with AI.
Identified workflow barriers hindering sales team success at All Cloud.
Generated over $1 million in training revenue by focusing on behavioral change.
Designed systems that change behavior, not just transfer knowledge.
Presgen automatically generates presentations, edits, and narrates those videos.
Demonstrates a practical solution to sales enablement challenges.
Focus on reducing new hire ramp times from weeks to days.
Ensuring consistent messaging across hundreds of countries.
Innovate solutions for how sales teams work