Identified workflow obstacles hindering sales team effectiveness.
Designed systems to eliminate barriers and accelerate success.
Measured results through tangible business outcomes, like reduced ramp times.
Traditional training often fails to address underlying workflow issues.
Effective enablement focuses on removing obstacles, not just knowledge transfer.
Real-world experience at All Cloud highlighted the need for workflow solutions.
Presgen is a platform built to address the real problems faced by global sales teams.
Features include video editing and auto-presentation capabilities.
Demonstrates a commitment to innovation and practical solutions.
Reduced new hire ramp times from weeks to days.