Presgen assesses skills gaps and creates personalized training.
Technical Trainer with 27+ years of experience.
Aims to disrupt traditional education with AI-powered innovation.
Millions are overlooked for jobs due to missing skills.
Current training: expensive, generic, time-intensive
Learning one competency can take months.
Presgen Core: Generates tailored presentations.
Presgen Data: Analyzes data and inserts intelligent charts.
Presgen Video: Transforms content into engaging videos.
Presgen Training: AI-narrates AI-generated presentations
Advanced models → better content generation
OpenAI mentorship → optimized education AI
AI-powered education for everyone
Provides world-class training in resource-limited regions.
Presgen is a working platform ready to scale.
Grove partnership = global impact