Presgen assesses skills gaps and creates personalized training.
Technical Trainer with 27+ years of experience.
Disrupts traditional education with AI innovation.
Reimagines education for new possibilities.
Job seekers are overlooked due to specific skill gaps.
Millions are overlooked for jobs due to missing skills.
Current platforms offer expensive, generic courses.
Months of commitment are required for a single competency.
Presgen Core: Generates tailored presentations.
Presgen Data: Analyzes data and inserts intelligent charts.
Presgen Video: Transforms content into engaging videos.
Presgen Training: AI-narrates AI-generated presentations
Advanced models = better content generation
OpenAI mentorship = optimized education AI
Assesses current skills to identify gaps.
AI-powered education for everyone
Provides world-class training in resource-limited regions.
Presgen is a working platform ready to scale.
Grove partnership = global impact